The.
Eighth. Floor off.
The shore or.
In or Lloyd.
Or. In.
Or.
Anything with.
Her room. Eight
hundred. Fifty three.
Old.
Or old.
Or are. Or will.
When.
One or. More.
When it is quite convenient
I should like to speak with
a member of the. But you work out
you wish to see me I presume so.
Yes and I the pleasure of addressing Mr
Scrooge or Mr Mollett the mallet been dead
seven years oh. Darn it.
Seven years ago I spent
a night though we took the liberty of calling
on you with your chambers Mr Scrooge
thinking that you would finish business for
the day but we failed to make any money
here. And the only person is that
right Consequently we have called
at this festive season of the year Mr Scrooge
it seems more than usually desirable
to make some slight provision for the
poor and destitute who suffer terribly at
this present time when it thousands are
in want of common necessaries hundreds of
thousands are in want of common comforts.
Yes plenty of first on the union work out
his are still in operation there they are
still I wish I could say that were not
well known the Premier are in full vigor
then a very this is
a very very character that would promote
human senses something occurring to
interfere with them in their youthful God.
Under the impression that they scarcely
furnish Christmas cheer of mind and body
for the multitude some few of us are
endeavoring to raise
a fund to pay the poor of London meat and
drink and means of want we choose this
time because this is the time of all others
when want is keenly felt and abundance
rejoices Now what shall I
put you down for. Nothing
nothing at all see you wish to be
anonymous. I wish to be left alone
to kiss you ask me what is my wish
that. I don't make many myself
a Christmas I can't afford to make
a lot of idle people I have to support
the institution just mention they cost
enough people
a bed they are paid by to go there they
can't go there and then they would rather
die than if they'd rather die than better
do it. And decrease the population.
So if you still be dead I don't know that
but you should know it's done by business
man's got enough to do this
well by to that interview with
a lot of other people's mind
occupies me constantly.
I'm going to express my regrets
I said What do you think.
A. Man.
Doing with that. Right I think
your pardon said but the out of
office if you can see code and by fiat get
your facts. And sure to fit your facts
that yes that shows continued going out and
I thought I might that you could finish
it with
a small quantity Yes of course you know
it's very evident to me you know we do not
have to but always you know in particular
you don't pay for the call so you can
afford to be reckless that's already evident
to me said you know that my interest
is not your interest nor my willpower
your welfare. Nobody works out
I don't give you
a warm enough I'm not cold Why
should you be I mean I've seen your.
Great many years i Pad.
I don't know any of the Internet I'm lazy.
You have
a wife and family to support and. Yes. The
boys. And I have voted twice
a. And I.
Don't much of I can.
Have that.
Go. Away.
Much good has it done you much good will
it ever do you it's the only time I know
of in the tell of the year when then that
we've been seen by one consent to open
the shutouts the day the
fall so it's never put
a scrap of gold or still in the bucket I
believe it has done me good and will do me
good and I say God bless
it. Just to get it
if I hear another word from you you keep
your Christmas by losing your situation.
By the prophets because when you go to its
parliament Don't be angry and. I'll see
you why why. Why did you get
married because I've got
a love because I have good evening you
never came to see it happen I give that as
a reason for not coming now when I was.
Around when you want to do so you want to
disappoint you but you never had
a cold which I've been putting the wind
up in the bud pretty good eating well I'm
not in the heart to fight with. My baby
child and it's because. I kissed the tube
out of the two on this bit that the six
Haven't you yet your and so if you don't
know that what you are very good. To you
and many other not to get in your good day
to Mrs Bray today.
Always ready and willing to
take your work I know this.
If you want all day off
tomorrow. It's quite convenient
convenient. That. Oh my goodness you.
Don't think I miss you do you and I have
to bail all the day's wages no. You don't
have. A pretty good in
a man's pocket every December. I
suppose you've got to have it.
The key. It was Jesus the joy
early early next morning.
Good night and
a very crisp batch of the. NEW DAY.
A little.
Moon.
Enamored.
Moon Moon on the.
END.
When you go anywhere like. An explosion.
In your city the lights
Thank you. Soledad.
The old
old. Old
. A few.
Hundred.
Years of get out.
Of. A The.
Lyric. And move. You calling me
when I.
Am.
I. Only stop there.
I love it when you make your speech you
know all you want to convey to them to
remain continue to enjoy the. Call
of silence for the noir toast.
Me any. Way. I
know they do and Gentleman
great sign but I don't
see the lonesome out of redundant idle
thank you loads
they did send gentlemen almost
Gracious Majesty the Queen.
World a way to be a girl
a girl. Girl. World be
a war
a survey old world
a world war
the word the world
a warm. Day
where
a way. Right
people out there with. Or are.
A.
What.
The.
One the.
One.
The.
Where.
Man come.
Back.
Boy
a war with. One
.
With.
The.
What.
One.
Thank you.
You.
Only you could see me.
Oh. I would you.
Know about me. It is required of everyone
that the spirit within him to walk abroad
among his fellow men and if that spirit
goes not forth in life it is condemned to
do so after death. My S.
Ability never to be on the narrow limits
of our money changing. So I cannot lead.
I cannot take I cannot linger anywhere.
I where the chain I forged
in life. I made it linked I
think. You know the weight and length
of the call you bear yourself.
Words of comfort. Speak words
of comfort and comfort
I have to give am here to warn you
to save you that be possible to
war. To save me. From them
such
a fate just to wonder through the world
and witness what I cannot share but might
have shared on earth and turn to
happiness but you were always
a good man of business Jacob
business. My business
charity parents benevolence all
over my business as they should be.
Now me for my time is short you will be
haunted by three spirits without their
visit you cannot hope to shun the path I
tread. You shall behold the visions of
a Christmas past. A Christmas
present. End of Christmas Yet to
Come. Expect the first
when the clock strikes
midnight tonight.
Look to see more down.
In.
Where. World troop. I don't know.
Where.
Moon.
Is fitted to Christmas but. I am
here to show you the seams that have
the. Look back on the
Gulf of banished years.
The man is Jones been named so that's
impossible then I should have no alternative
but to take immediate steps to cover it but
you must see that if that is the way I
get an idea. I don't mean. Something
that is precisely what I do which. I couldn't
place in the hospital even though the
guy may have gone you.
Know I'm going to do
a new. Job given
a lot of weeks. When
.
You know you've given. The.
Choice. To me when they.
Join a man without
a hitch and I'm sure most ways
everything in this case probably. I.
Couldn't help. Just business if I would do
without sentiment to enter this country
house I should be in the bank
to go to the new year as
a couple just going out with just your
life list about them listed just.
As I could not and now void
things that you all must. Your
good month. Also uses the priests and
a time in which to pay its bills the next
I'm going to make allowances the old
feelings when I was asked
to be my this is this is
a when you maybe I should just.
Make the news just like. But it is
a given to me but not
a bit I don't even. Know.
That you know me and growth and you gain
the ability to grow so I never change
would you. Change.
You know me. And be. Happy.
That I chose.
To.
You. And see that. It's.
OK.
It's.
About the way about as
a friend of yours is up to
you what you'll get. How can
I do. It But Mr Scrooge Mr Scrooge
it was up. Part of the office will
never was not shut up in the with
a candle inside I could scarcely help she.
Is populism on the point of this idea.
There you sat alone quite alone
in the world I do believe.
Did it I cannot bear it all the
number all. The shadows just.
Have to say I must say I do not.
When I'm drunk I know it's.
You. Who. Know me.
And know me better. I.
Mean. You have never.
Seen the like of me. Never. Never was.
The young. Meaning I am. My elder brother.
Or in the later years. I don't
think. I'm afraid I have not.
Any practice. Now. Eighteen
hundred. And then spend
an entire night still.
Already I have been for. If
you have
a. Ritual
so. Keeps Christmas.
My role.
Thank you.
On both. Fronts.
You. Slowly.
But. It. Was
a day just to press the target on your God
that's not him and he's just about the
want to make the most by helping the oh
it's because they're still hot five tales
from. The face. Of The Creator that.
We did didn't need to finish up last night
and had to get away to school never mind
is always you walk out I'm going to
go on it before the fog you do Will.
Your rear end. I wrote about sees them
enough coming. No copying.
No I mean. Did.
I miss it.
And if you. Do remember.
The.
Weekend doesn't. Say.
What the about to receive
made a noise makers to anything but
a me if. I knew nobody about. What
I do with the boss I happened to continue.
With the management and to was. Told
by the printer that I didn't like the
combination we should remember on TOG I get
you. It is to.
Accept best we ever had about
a new game on why did you love
and even now we haven't even to
go
a lot. To. Get
the. Mind yet
regarding the move it is Christian
putting. When you look pale
my love and you know that I
am. An anxious on the putting
a hypno. I'm going to. Do you show me.
You don't I'm anxious about that could.
Be gone
a long time. The putting it through can
tell you not to promise on supposing that
somebody has got over the
back wall and today I.
Wish you were gone why
do you. Want. Everyone.
Tells me the time. When. They can see.
Actually the. Name of.
The child. Is like.
Adding up and they're going.
To stop US population.
Than you. Have discovered
about the subject. When you
decide what men shall live
when men Guy It may be that in
the sight of Heaven. That's.
A man's child. Toast I give you Mrs screw
the feast I'll do the feast Indeed I wish
I had you here I've given that piece of
my mind to feast about I hope you have
a good appetite for I took my do you know
the children's Christmas to be Christmas
Day I'm sure on which one thinks the health
of such an odious stingy on feeling bad
as Mr Scrooge you know he is rather nobody
knows it better than you do my Christmas
. Well I'll drink his health for your
sake of the days not his He'll be.
Very happy I've no doubt. Mr Scrooge
is help now keep going altogether Mr
Scrooge. Mr. I need this help.
And now I need to do is yes yes and
given to me once you take the handle
Yes however the hot.
Tea.
From the oil and shallow
waters. It would change the
world where
world. Where.
The. World.
Would. Be
a world where the.
Real. World.
Where. It was two years
a go.
Girl.
World. I was what I was
the Iraq war was up up
up up up up up up and he
said. That's what I thought. I did because
he did do that watching all these
stories across the globe below and that's
the truth he isn't focused because he
might be Vince's good and punishment and
I have nothing to say against him but
Johnny that he bitch I think you want to
tell me what of that idea is what is it to
you stood he doesn't do any good with any
call making you feel comfortable with yes
even the Senate fix the thinking that
is and I do benefit that some of it.
But I know they can figure out why
have I decided. And yes if they get
to do is head to this like US naval and
even government guiding us. Well what are
you going to play when. I know. What
the following the present and that of
knowledge is a bit of an animal
a savage animal and animal on the ground
who don't live in London yes that
is the major show although I've never run
through no is no although I love it so I
. Do not.
Yet.
Close to the future I fear
you. Know I have seen.
A LOT ABOUT TO SCHOOL the shadows of
the things that have not. But will be.
A lesson I hope to live to
be. Another man like I was.
Prepared. To pay.
I don't know much about it either way I
only know he did. Not have a prior was
a matter with him I thought he'd never
have. Wanted I was his manager at the to
his company perhaps as an
epitome That's all I know.
Because God is only a plow so
I'm told the whole is. Not
a skater I don't know I've got something
else to think about. I do not see myself
in my accustomed place when
where and. When I am I
not there.
I'm around. A mix of. Let the
child woman and the Beatles learn the longest
amount of the the second and the next
the undertaker's men as Elm
can be that no hero Joe has
a job if we have no free media
without meaning I'm not.
Going to make you know with the
mission I mean to the planet.
I. Don't. And there
standing in the world for
a full month the was. Like
this is not good man.
How can this. One let me know
that you want it. Right. Not
right.
Your to help. Me give
another six words. Now.
I always did too much too late the
two week mission my. And now on
to.
A good.
Things are known within laying. Off
you were born to make or didn't
and you would certainly do
we. Blanket each blanket.
Like you to take over
without. You anything catchin
to be afraid of that. Not flew
back until I was like me when
find. Is the best he had
it in a big light did
a bit that. You know with
putting it on the big
individual.
But having. The fun of
a low godly Avenue and that while. This
is the. Way it's like never run
away from him when he was alive
to plow the job when he was dead just.
A case of this I'm happy man might be
my own. My life dead ends that way
now. What
is the best.
The man they spoke of. Neglected.
Broke. Can you not
so vain. I'm kinda this. Connected with.
Child any mention of.
How this is my eyes. It's
a week by candlelight. I wouldn't show
we just your father who comes. To see us
time busted brother. If
you want to slow down
a new speech last night.
I've known you with.
I've known to walk with Tiger
when he showed up very fast.
But he was very like to Kenny and his
father loved him so it was no trouble no
trouble.
Your father Bill. Read my dear
promise. And. But.
You would have been quick will be done long
before Sunday something you would today
the yes my dear I've seen
but I Tiny Tim is to rest.
Done you good to see how green at least.
I promised him we would
walk there are some.
Live in the truth or.
I mean Mr Scrooge is near you today and
he said to me I am heartily sorry for you
Mr Pritchett and heartily sorry for
your good bye so how did you get.
No idea why that you would
a good wife everybody knows
that where I lived. And
he did. The service any service
that I could do for you
great comfort. It almost seemed
as though he had no title.
And felt. And I'm sure.
None of us forget you. Know
this first part that is the.
And I know. That when we recorded how.
Although he was but it is
a child. We shall not
quite. Nice. And to get our
tiny.
I'm very happy. Now spin it
tell me. What man that was.
A.
Little nearer to the stern. Right tell me
how he says he goes to pieces with.
The chatter to the things that
maybe.
I don't know the man I
was. I ended up with
a man I must have been born with as
intercourse. Should be this if it is old to
name. Then a wife expunge away
the right to know. I've been on
a Kiss my hot wife you can hold
your. I believe in the past the
present and the future. The speech of
all to see should strive within me.
I will not shut my eyes
this is the place feet. No.
Will. I will be of.
The House the president of the future
will Jacob. Ever know Christmas does
play just put this. Into.
Thank you Jacob. To me. To.
Not Thomas notice. That I'm not on down.
Would be maybe this goes his way out.
Of the way of.
And then to Christmas. This year.
It is an angel. It is
a drunken man. Because. That video.
Of
a girl missing. Goes. Like
this don't you don't have.
A way. To manage this mess did.
I do I haven't is that. Just
a little thing like. A. Good
to go to the street they.
Get
a job for you of pocket boy. You know they
sell the price tag of the bedding and then
. You go
inside you bring it back here and I'll tell
you where to take it when you come back
with the man and I'll give your chin and
you come back you might get it should I.
Call I have. I think I'm going to send
it's divided by count the credit.
Cards from. It is twice the
size of guided him he's not de
Janeiro you're not.
High.
Narrow.
Well you. Should move to the
left I'm doomed I've got to have
a ticket. Or wait a minute wait
a minute. You go get me
my overcoat in the head.
I jump in on. And go to the bathroom.
And get there at the bit.
Where.
Narrow.
If you will the shop.
I'm in this mess if you show that price
deck you go get the big one I mean now.
I.
Like. The new. Five hundred because
you've got to read not if I
place much by predatory in the way I.
Do manage to make this in the.
Us as nice. As the Matrix movie.
The.
Candidate for the kitchen
it will never get to
a well I'd like as you suggest there's
a lot of it and there's the money
you know very kind of you to
a profit. With
a Christmas idea that
same young. Blood would
take it with. This mystery I hope to
see just issue yes that's my name
I'm not even in front for you but when
you're not with was your father. And you
should be good enough to put
me down. Must have missed this
whole round yet another I mean it's not
like I said I'm afraid I'm in effect
payments into the fire just to come out
and see me you can come out we will leave
YOU THANK YOU THANK YOU THANK
YOU place you've just been in
a few. Close calls.
Like.
Your master in my idea. Can
I see him by that. Kind of
action you know that even knows me.
Yet you. Know I.
Prayed less like knows
this it is-I your Uncle
Scrooge I've come to dinner
when you let him Fred.
Come well why
a Merry Christmas to you Uncle
Tommy I mean the joy in this.
Winter months and then he Chris thank
you my dear and very Christmas too
old. Christmas.
The.
Not to come from. The usual.
I don't think about.
It.
Do you do. What you mean like
I mean you're just not ready.
And
a charge that. I am behind my back I think
you have to act I think you are the one
to give us
a chance he repeated I was making rather
big. So I didn't want to do besides
I'm not going to stand it
any. And then after all.
That I said you're crazy just
because. You were the most
cities you know besides I got your
very serious and expedited. Lot of
calls. On the work day making sure
that their money and they bought the
deposit you say the minute
it's gone. I'm adding
a Christmas. My good fellow that
I've given you from if you. Are
one I'll go on the ruling.
Against the wall the war will
never be doing the way or the god oh. They
were. All the old.
The A The old the
the
a. A A
the. Low.
A A the. The.
Off off
off. Off.